{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963398949","data":{"timestamp":" 946963398949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963406391","data":{"timestamp":" 946963406391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963412509","data":{"timestamp":" 946963412509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963422988","data":{"timestamp":" 946963422988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963442181","data":{"timestamp":" 946963442181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s_pu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963450717","data":{"timestamp":" 946963450717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_z_nu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963458495","data":{"timestamp":" 946963458494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_mu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963469156","data":{"timestamp":" 946963469156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_oga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963478604","data":{"timestamp":" 946963478604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963483883","data":{"timestamp":" 946963483883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963494053","data":{"timestamp":" 946963494053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963503151","data":{"timestamp":" 946963503151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_ivo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963504871","data":{"timestamp":" 946963504871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_t_ivo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963510621","data":{"timestamp":" 946963510621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" f0cb0b30-8f4b-4184-ae57-59dba66d01a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_t_ivo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963525608","data":{"timestamp":" 946963525608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 9cf2ea36-3cb0-4316-9eaf-5fd1f5863640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walifurahi_alichukuwa-walikimbia-walifurahi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walifurahi"," userResponse":" walifurahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963532635","data":{"timestamp":" 946963532635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 9cf2ea36-3cb0-4316-9eaf-5fd1f5863640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kushangaza"," userResponse":" kushangaza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963533267","data":{"timestamp":" 946963533267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 9cf2ea36-3cb0-4316-9eaf-5fd1f5863640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963541227","data":{"timestamp":" 946963541227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 9cf2ea36-3cb0-4316-9eaf-5fd1f5863640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.noShow.14__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kushangaza_nimpendaye-kuwasaidia-kushangaza"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963552579","data":{"timestamp":" 946963552579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963554750","data":{"timestamp":" 946963554750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963557475","data":{"timestamp":" 946963557475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963559201","data":{"timestamp":" 946963559201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963565734","data":{"timestamp":" 946963565733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963568070","data":{"timestamp":" 946963568070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963569657","data":{"timestamp":" 946963569656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963572610","data":{"timestamp":" 946963572609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963574809","data":{"timestamp":" 946963574809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963578051","data":{"timestamp":" 946963578051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963581596","data":{"timestamp":" 946963581596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963584182","data":{"timestamp":" 946963584182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963586261","data":{"timestamp":" 946963586261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963589520","data":{"timestamp":" 946963589520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963592238","data":{"timestamp":" 946963592238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963596894","data":{"timestamp":" 946963596894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963599149","data":{"timestamp":" 946963599148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963617421","data":{"timestamp":" 946963617421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963619333","data":{"timestamp":" 946963619333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963621084","data":{"timestamp":" 946963621084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963623049","data":{"timestamp":" 946963623048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963625187","data":{"timestamp":" 946963625187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963630126","data":{"timestamp":" 946963630126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963632610","data":{"timestamp":" 946963632610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_CHUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963635513","data":{"timestamp":" 946963635513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963638418","data":{"timestamp":" 946963638417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963639588","data":{"timestamp":" 946963639588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963641263","data":{"timestamp":" 946963641263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963642024","data":{"timestamp":" 946963642024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963642034","data":{"timestamp":" 946963642033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963644134","data":{"timestamp":" 946963644134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963645307","data":{"timestamp":" 946963645307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963648371","data":{"timestamp":" 946963648371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963650403","data":{"timestamp":" 946963650403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963652557","data":{"timestamp":" 946963652556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963654593","data":{"timestamp":" 946963654593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963656334","data":{"timestamp":" 946963656334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963659110","data":{"timestamp":" 946963659110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963660573","data":{"timestamp":" 946963660573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963665031","data":{"timestamp":" 946963665031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963666484","data":{"timestamp":" 946963666484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963668445","data":{"timestamp":" 946963668445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963670317","data":{"timestamp":" 946963670316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963674476","data":{"timestamp":" 946963674476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963676752","data":{"timestamp":" 946963676751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963678781","data":{"timestamp":" 946963678781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963680328","data":{"timestamp":" 946963680328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963682172","data":{"timestamp":" 946963682172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963684303","data":{"timestamp":" 946963684303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963685897","data":{"timestamp":" 946963685896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963687101","data":{"timestamp":" 946963687101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963688707","data":{"timestamp":" 946963688707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963691107","data":{"timestamp":" 946963691107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963694564","data":{"timestamp":" 946963694564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963696579","data":{"timestamp":" 946963696579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963699585","data":{"timestamp":" 946963699583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963703056","data":{"timestamp":" 946963703055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963704798","data":{"timestamp":" 946963704798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963706314","data":{"timestamp":" 946963706314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963708826","data":{"timestamp":" 946963708825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963710614","data":{"timestamp":" 946963710614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963712032","data":{"timestamp":" 946963712032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963712436","data":{"timestamp":" 946963712436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963715223","data":{"timestamp":" 946963715222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963719744","data":{"timestamp":" 946963719744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963723674","data":{"timestamp":" 946963723674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963726928","data":{"timestamp":" 946963726928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963728667","data":{"timestamp":" 946963728667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963730275","data":{"timestamp":" 946963730275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963734558","data":{"timestamp":" 946963734558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963736517","data":{"timestamp":" 946963736517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963738041","data":{"timestamp":" 946963738041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963740363","data":{"timestamp":" 946963740363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963742573","data":{"timestamp":" 946963742573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963744763","data":{"timestamp":" 946963744763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963746559","data":{"timestamp":" 946963746559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963748512","data":{"timestamp":" 946963748511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963754064","data":{"timestamp":" 946963754064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963756303","data":{"timestamp":" 946963756302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963759560","data":{"timestamp":" 946963759560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963761507","data":{"timestamp":" 946963761506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963763890","data":{"timestamp":" 946963763890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963766075","data":{"timestamp":" 946963766075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963772724","data":{"timestamp":" 946963772724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963776029","data":{"timestamp":" 946963776029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963778084","data":{"timestamp":" 946963778084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963779811","data":{"timestamp":" 946963779811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963782405","data":{"timestamp":" 946963782405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963785136","data":{"timestamp":" 946963785136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963787149","data":{"timestamp":" 946963787148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963787309","data":{"timestamp":" 946963787309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" 1351b98f-c5c1-4d9e-97f3-e08a244c134e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963801001","data":{"timestamp":" 946963801000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963802803","data":{"timestamp":" 946963802803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963804931","data":{"timestamp":" 946963804931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963806545","data":{"timestamp":" 946963806544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963808885","data":{"timestamp":" 946963808884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963810638","data":{"timestamp":" 946963810637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963812994","data":{"timestamp":" 946963812994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963815347","data":{"timestamp":" 946963815347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963818251","data":{"timestamp":" 946963818251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963821072","data":{"timestamp":" 946963821072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963826102","data":{"timestamp":" 946963826102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963828367","data":{"timestamp":" 946963828367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963830040","data":{"timestamp":" 946963830040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963832999","data":{"timestamp":" 946963832999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963835173","data":{"timestamp":" 946963835173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963837283","data":{"timestamp":" 946963837283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963840947","data":{"timestamp":" 946963840947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963842891","data":{"timestamp":" 946963842891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963847002","data":{"timestamp":" 946963847002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963847134","data":{"timestamp":" 946963847134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_082312"," gameId":" b5c74d16-da03-4ecd-86a6-5fc6e474a1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}